grateful to have him in the CTVB
Discord. Like he's he's been dropping
crazy stuff. Um and he said next time
he's like, "Oh man, next time I find
something like this, I'm not going to
post it on Twitter. I'm just going to
put it in the the cool research channel
on the CTV Discord." I'm like, "Yes, you
should have done that." Yeah.
Best part of backing when you can just,
you know, critical think, right?
[Music]
Yeah, dude.
Sup, hackers? Welcome to the This Week
in Bug Bounty segment where we talk
about hackers that are rocking it,
programs that are rocking it, and cool
opportunities for you, the listener. Um,
so let's jump right into it. First one
up this week is actually a write up
about yours truly from Bug Crowd, the
hacker spotlight for Rhino Reader. Um,
yeah, so if you want to get to know me a
little bit better, then this write up
contains a lot of the information that
we kind of skim over on uh on the pod.
Um, so definitely definitely check it
out if you're up for that. Uh but the
real update here was that a new program
launched on Bug Crowd um which is called
Ultramo. Now you know new programs pop
up all the time. We try to keep you up
to date on that. But this one's
specifically interesting because Ultramo
is not what it sounds like or at least
it's not what I thought it was in the
first place. It's actually Mint Mobile.
Yeah, that's right. The one that with
all the crazy commercials with Ryan
Reynolds and that sort of thing. Um, so
we always talk about hack about hack on
brands that you're excited about or that
you're, you know, that you use. Um, and
I think this is a great opportunity to
do that. Um, this one just went public
not too long ago. This specific program
is for their mobile scope, but they also
have web scope uh that is in in scope of
another public program. So definitely
check them out if you're interested in
hacking on Mint Mobile and then you can
tell your friends you hacked Ryan
Reynolds or whatever. Um, all right. On
the similar vein of good programs, uh I
also wanted to highlight John Deere.
Okay. Um I a lot of people, Reszo
included, the co-host of the podcast,
have had a tremendous experience on the
John Deere program. Um they are public
about the fact that they have a private
program. Uh here's a write up right here
on their website that uh talks about how
they paid $1.5 million through their
private program. Um but they also have a
VDP. So, this is a good opportunity for
you guys that uh kind of want to jump
the jump the queue here and hack on a
program or a VDP that will get you
access to a BBP. Um, then this could be
a good opportunity to do that. The
reviews have been amazing. The team
sounds awesome. So, uh, definitely check
that out if you're interested. All
right. And last up, we have from Yes, We
Hack, uh, the Yes We Hack Dojo. Now, if
you guys haven't checked out the Yes, We
Hack dojo, I I have to admit I was kind
of sleeping on it a little bit, too. But
these are like pretty technical
challenges that they're putting out
every week that um really help you
understand some pretty core
technologies. Um and this week they've
launched one called Ruby Treasure. I
won't give up uh too much information
about it, but it's definitely worth
checking out um if you want to try to
hack Ruby related targets. Um all right,
that's all we got for the this week in
Bug Bounty segment. Let's go back to the
show. All right, man. I guess we kind of
owe the listeners an apology, right? cuz
we've had we've had this this Google uh
podcast stuck in approval hell for what
three three weeks now? Three weeks.
Yeah. Yeah, dude. Um so guys, I promise
it's coming. It is coming. And it's a
good ass episode, don't you? Don't you
think, man? It is. Yeah, it really is.
It's both fun, entertaining, and
extremely informative and really long,
too. So, lots of lots of good lots of
good insights. I think it's like two
something hours. Um, we we interview uh
one of the Google employees, get some of
his cool war stories, and then we also
spend a long time sort of
debriefing the the dubs uh over there in
Tokyo uh let me just say for everyone,
it's not for lack of trying. Justin is a
very persistent uh hounder of people.
So, and he car he cares very deeply
about getting this stuff out. So, just
so you all know, we're fighting on your
behalf. Yeah. Yeah, I really do. And and
I I definitely I mean I'm not going to
say I made an enemy, you know, at
Google, but their PR person definitely
like I'm sure is not pleased with me cuz
I'm like, "Hey, hey, when is it
approved? When is it approved?" And and
to be honest, you know, at the end of
the day, they're doing their best to get
it approved and uh and I know their team
is. There's just a lot of logistic stuff
that's come up. But yeah, um be be
patient with us. It is coming and
hopefully it'll be out the week after
this episode is out. So, yep, that
that's that's what they've committed to
this time. So, hopefully that'll that'll
actually happen. Um, all right, man. We
have a lot of stuff to get to and only
about an hour uh maybe even less to get
to it. So, let's jump right in. Um, the
biggest news I think of this week is the
Swansonzer zero day uh in in Chrome.
Yeah, you went deep on this so much so
that you were like not replying to
things and you were like looking into it
and you started a whole little hackalong
thing. So, tell tell me about it. Yeah.
Okay. So, um, here's the deal. Uh, so
we're recording this episode. Thank you,
our production team. Sorry. I know this
is going out late, but we're recording
this episode on May 7th. On May 5th at 1
p.m., Slunzer tweeted something out and
then uh proceeded to drop the tweet in
the cool research um channel in in our
Discord saying, "Hey, uh, check out this
technique." And essentially what this
allows uh the attacker to do is if you
have an image injection on any page
loading from your attacker controlled
server, you can leak the query
parameters of the the page where that
image is injected to the attacker
controlled server. So when you say image
injection, do you mean you have to like
be able to inject the image tag or
literally just by being able to inject a
URL there? It it it could be anything.
like we we um uh I think Jorian Demo, a
couple other people from the Discord did
a little like followup on this
afterwards, myself as well. Um and they
found out that this technique applies
to, you know, say you're injecting in
the source of an image tag. It, you
know, that's loaded on the page. It
could be a dynamically generated image
tag. It could be CSS background URL. It
could be anything essentially that loads
an image. This but all you need is all
you need is that injection point. You
don't have to be able to put in the tag.
you just need like literally the URL
just to control the source, right? Um
which is super super duper common. Yeah.
So common. Yeah. And and it used to be
it used to be that this was the default,
right? When the referer would just you
know yeet out the full, you know,
location. Href to whatever server it
connected to. But then a couple years
back they they said actually we're just
going to put the origin in the refer
header. Um, but the way that Slanzer
does this and uh I'll go ahead and and
share my screen here. Sure. Is he um
responds with a header.
Here it is right here. He responds with
a link header in the response of that
image. Now this link header um is then
processed by the browser and
unfortunately in that link header you
can set the referral policy right which
controls what data is sent in the
referer. Um, and it it also allows to
specify a preload, right? Um, and
essentially what this does then is when
they load the URL that's returned in
that that link header, it leaks the the
full location.href, right, to the
preload request that's being defined in
the link header um because of that
unsafe uh URL referral policy specified.
So, really cool stuff. Is like a is link
are link headers pretty common? I mean,
obviously, I've been hacking for a while
and I don't I don't see them very often
or I haven't I haven't like heard much
about them. So, is this like a common
known thing? No, it's not. I mean, this
this and unfortunately I I kind of stuck
my foot in my mouth a little bit here.
Let me see if I can uh immediately tag
the person to fix it. Yeah. Yeah, dude.
I immediately tagged uh Jing Kokatu from
Google and he's like, "Why did you tag
me in this? I will I will fix this
immediately." I'm like, "Shit, I
shouldn't have done that." Um, so you
know and and and it works out in the end
it works out because um I think Slanzer
you know he he had been trying to get
this acknowledged by the Google team and
saying hey you should not load link
headers on sub resources of pages uh
that because that's not a good idea and
Google was like eh I you know it's not
that big of a deal but then when it get
gets a bunch of PR via this tweet um
then I think they're looking to make a
change now but as a lot of people in the
community dead. It's going to be a long
uh deprecation period. Why is that? You
know, just because like all their stuff
that rolls out could have downstream
effects and they just need to make sure
they don't break support for like
enterprise clients and that sort of
thing. Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. And and and
I think also, you know, it's it's a um
the link header despite, you know, this
specific scenario probably being a
little bit uh more more difficult uh or
more nuanced, the link header is used,
you know. So June unfortunately also
killed the uh the Japanese character set
thing that we people have been using uh
to to get XSS. Um and that one was a
little bit easier to deprecate because
of the fact that nobody's using that.
Yeah. Um but uh the character said
sniffing. I mean um and this one I think
is going to be a little bit different.
So I think we've got at least a year of
we can exploit this. I I I do that.
That's my professional guess. But if
June has anything to say about it, it
might be faster. Yeah, that's sweet.
Yeah. And the other thing I wanted to
shout out on this, dude. Okay. Well,
okay. So, there's like five tweets that
go along with this. Okay. Y So, um
here's the tweet that I did sort of as a
recap of this whole thing because this
really is gamechanging, right? Like this
completely removes a entire a security
boundary that's been in place for years.
Um so the the first thing that I kind of
wanted to that I specified in the the
summary of this um vulnerability was
that this can be done recursively with
multiple links. So you you can you can
say okay
um provide the link header with a with a
preload um URL and then provide another
one with a pre-load URL and then those
preloads can also return link headers.
Okay. And so essentially you can do it
recursively over and over and over again
and create a consistent stream of um
requests coming from the user's browser
uh with a single image source load.
Isn't that like sick? Yeah. But I I
guess what's the benefit to just doing
it the once? Like why why would give me
some attack scenarios? Yeah. So, I mean,
ju just the once is is good enough to
leak the the um you know, refer, but if
you want to do it time and time again,
there's a couple things that that could
apply to. Um one, you can because
prefetches are set with um are sending
cookies with them, you could do a uh
zeroclick getbased curve uh exploitation
if you have an image injection that uh
would be Oh, that's interesting. Right.
And it also enables it if you have to
brute force an ID. So let's say for
example I've got a get basic surf, but I
need a numeric ID and I know it's going
to take like 200 requests to do it,
right? I could use this to like do a
bunch of requests from the victim's
browser and trigger that get based curve
potentially with zero click by getting
just an image injection on the like
users dashboard or something. Wow. Yeah.
Honestly, I really hope somebody pulls
that off. That is sick. Yeah. Yeah. So
So that's that's one of them. Um very
cool stuff. The second one was this
which was really interesting. Um we also
have access to setting media queries
here which is also an attribute of the
link um tag. So we can specify almost
like CSS like syntax that will be run in
the victim's environment just by loading
a tag. Unfortunately media queries are
pretty limited at this point. Pretty
much the only useful thing we can link
is like or leak is like the the the
viewport size which can tell us whether
we're like in an iframe or whatever. But
it could be useful for cross-sight
leaks. I definitely would imagine that
this will pop up in a CTF at some point.
Yeah. Um but I I think there's
definitely additional impact there. Um
and then the the third one here is that
uh prefetch which is the one that that
is is being used here isn't the only um
directive rail directive in the link
header uh that can be used uh here. So
there's also other ones like compression
dictionary, module preload and preload.
Um, and the one that's really
interesting here is is um compression
dictionary because what that allows you
to do is force the browser to download a
dictionary that is then used to
decompress following requests being
made. Okay. Um, so you can like modify
the the uh the contents of those
requests. Um, but I I played around with
it for a little while and I just can't
get it to do anything super interesting.
Yeah. So that's where that's where my
mind went immediately when you show me
that unsafe um unsafe URL part is like
that those like um little parameters
that are uh a part of the link header
like what all options do you have there
that you could set that could
potentially do other things that are
malicious. Yeah. So I I like went down
the rabbit hole on that. There's a
couple that look really really promising
like you can set the the you can hint at
a content type but it's not the content
type they actually use. It's just the
one that the browser actually like uh is
hinted at. So it it knows when to load
this. You can give it priority. You can
say this is a high priority request or a
low priority request, which you might be
able to do something with that. Um but
yeah, and then last but not least, um as
I mentioned before, this works with any
type of image injection pretty much. You
could be HTML image tag, could be
dynamically generated images, could be
CSS background images, could be uh font
face sources even. Um so there's like
this is also super impactful to CSS
injection. uh because previously CSS
injection didn't have a way to to leak
the query parameters um and now we do.
So pretty sick stuff. As far as
remediation goes,
um there is pretty much not a great way
to remediate this. uh the only options
you you you have are you a strict CSP
image source um uh to prevent the
attacker from getting the image
injection in the first place or a strict
default source which is even harder to
implement um to prevent the prefetch
request uh so is there any way for a web
app developer to develop safely a web
app that can use user um user selected
URLs for pulling in images or no
Man, I'm trying to think about it. I
mean, so basically server side, they're
gonna have to like download it and then
host it themselves, right? So that then
they can set that um safe I have no
Yeah. safe domain to pull from. Maybe
like a Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe they have
to use one of those like image proxies
or something like that, right? Could
they could they drop the link header?
Are they able to do that? Not if they're
not because the browser is doing it, not
not the code, right? Service worker. I
don't I don't know, man. It's pretty
It's pretty rough. I mean, the the best
bet right now is to just make sure that
if you're loading user supplied images
on the page, you should proxy it through
something like, you know, one of those
slashimage slash and then you put the
URL in the path, which is that's a tough
fix. That's a pretty that's a pretty
like heavy lift for a lot of companies,
especially I feel like honestly the
majority of companies that have user
supplied links to URLs and stuff,
they're like smaller companies or like
SMBs or, you know, like that sort of
thing. Cuz I feel like whenever you're
at a huge enterprise scale, you do have
some sort of
proxy or caching or downloading it. And
so, man, that's going to be a tough fix
for companies and it's like so
impactful, too. I wonder if if the
community comes up with a good
remediation, definitely share it with us
because I think people could throw that
in their reports as a really great way
to show impact like, hey, here's your
oneclick ATO. Here's your thing you can
implement to fix it. Yeah. I wonder if
you man I want to say I I was thinking
like I wonder if you could just set the
referer policy directly on the image but
I think it doesn't respect it because
the link header that's getting injected
is the thing that is yeah so nuts kind
of crazy but anyway the last thing I
wanted to say on all that was I have um
three
different people tweeting out here
saying like yep just got one click atto
via this yep got one click atto yep got
one click atto so people are milking
this already. Um, and and to be clear,
you know, this isn't a vulnerability in
and of itself. Like you have to land an
OOTH code on the page where that image
is injected, right? And that's how you
leak it via the an unconsumed OOTH code.
Um, you know, that's how you get it to
um not be consumed and then you leak it
out by the refer and that's how you get
at. Um, so could you leak other
sensitive things besides ooth codes
though? There's probably a lot of setups
where there are other interesting things
that can be linked. Leaked. Yeah. you
know, where where the user controls the
return URL. I mean, I haven't seen it a
lot, but I mean, it's definitely out
there. But, props to these people. I
mean, I don't know if they just like
jumped on it and were like got lucky or
if they knew in advance. I remember
seeing this. Yeah. Or they had notes.
Yep. Exactly. Yeah. All right. So, I
think that's everything. You know,
Sonzer has been uh releasing some really
good stuff and I I feel uh super
grateful to have him in the CTVB
Discord. like he's he's been dropping
crazy stuff. Um and he said next time
he's like, "Oh man, next time I find
something like this, I'm not going to
post it on Twitter. I'm just going to
put it in the the cool research channel
on the CTV Discord." I'm like, "Yes."
Yeah, you should have done that. Yeah.
Yeah. All right, man. What you got? Um
Yeah. So, we're going to both kind of go
down the list. I would say the first
thing, which is maybe like one of one of
the really cool writeups, it's on
Medium. Um Sharon Brisenoff. Uh if you
Oh, yeah. If you want to pod Yeah. um if
he he should post on something else
besides Medium. I'm so I'm so passionate
about people having their own blogs like
you know get your own stuff, you know,
like just like get your own credit for
it, you know, get build your own brand
for it. But anyways, yeah. So, um I
actually didn't know he was on the
podcast. So, yeah, he came on before. I
think that was in that that transition
period back in November. So, Okay. Yeah.
Cool. It was an awesome episode though,
man. I mean, like he is phenomenal.
Okay. I will definitely go back and
listen to it. Yeah. This to me is like
the classic uh bug bug hunter path
towards finding a bunch of
vulnerabilities. Let me see if I can
share it real quick while I'm talking
for the listeners. Share screen. Okay,
here we go. Um so how I made 64k from
deleted files a bug bounty story. Um it
wouldn't surprise me if there's still
lots of reports out there pending on
this but um basically he did what many
people have done which is you know try
to search for secrets in GitHub repos.
But the way he did it was at like a very
large scale and also using very smart
deep kind of git technique. So you can
look into this but he you know looked
for both dangling files and unpacked
pack files and um I'm sure you know most
of our listeners are familiar with git.
Um but there are ways in which you can
leave previously like scrubbed commits
um in the history and it's it's
non-trivial to go through this. I don't
know Justin if you've ever went down
this path before. I did this for Elastic
back in the day and they have so many
repos and they're so huge and the
history makes them even larger. I mean,
you really do need like terabytes to be
able to actually um pull these down and
then yeah, you'll run out of disc space
very very quickly. Yeah. So the way that
he did this was like really cool and
really smart but um you know he
recommends how you know how git
internally works but then he um
specifically um iterated over a bunch of
programs that um he's in and then
specifically went through the actual git
commit history which I think is really
powerful and um and then kind of I think
just went deeper than anyone else has
before and at a scale that people
haven't before and then specifically you
want to recover deleted files and then
you know if they don't delete it in a
very specific way it's still exposed
like you're still able to get it through
get through the history and um so
anyways that's what he did you can read
it um it's very interesting um I'm sure
there's still low hanging fruit
especially amongst a lot of private
programs like he's not in every possible
private program on the planet right and
then he and maybe he is on all the
private programs on like one platform
but there's many bug bounty platforms so
you could literally just replicate what
he did for only your private programs it
would use less disc space than doing all
the public ones and then you also
wouldn't dupe with him on a bunch of
these. I think that'd be a really
valuable and um high quality way to
attack. So, well, one of the things he
said in here which was really
interesting was that these so what
happens in git when you you know remove
something is that it becomes sort of
unlin the the file is still there,
right? And but it becomes unlin to the
specific commit, right? And what he said
is that it stays in the GitHub repo for
like two weeks or something like that.
I'm trying to let me see if I can find
the actual um because I know that they
are typically retained for around two
weeks before being eligible for garbage
collection the the deleted files. Um and
so this is something that we need to be
looking at you know over time. Yeah. And
and unless you said they do like this
whole rebase and like restart the whole
git repo then the deleted files are
still going to be there. Um and this is
something man you know I did this back
in the day. I did this, you know, a long
time ago. I had a full automation for
this. Tom Num Nom was the first guy that
introduced me to this back in like 2018.
Um, but these things come in cycles, you
know, and and and uh you know, Chiron
just got the the latest cycle of it. Um,
which is cool. Um, I will say one thing
was cool, the way he used AI to like
find more repos. Like I think this is
like the fact that these tools are, you
know, basically free or really cheap and
then they'll do a bunch of research for
you on your behalf, I think is still
being underutilized. Obviously, I talk a
lot about AI, but I think that um
specifically things like 03 and like
deep research on Gemini and stuff like
it it can find a lot of information very
quickly because obviously it's not
getting tripped up by captions because
they're either using indexes or they've
got, you know, working relationships
with the uh providers. So they're able
to mine data really well for things like
this. Actually, that'd be a good
transition into the tool I made because
because I threw because I threw Open AAI
into it recently. Did you see that
change? Yeah. Yeah. Good. Good. Good.
Well, hold on before we jump to that
here. I I'll I'll share my screen since
you just you can get the next one ready.
But um I wanted to say one more thing
that was really cool about this
research, which is he he shared he just
used truffle hog for all this. So it's
not like he's grepping for like a super
secret list of API keys, which is really
cool. And then but he said, you know,
these are the secrets that caused the
most impact. And at the top of the list
was GCP project and AWS uh production
tokens. Um so definitely, you know, we
got to keep an And then he shows one
right here of like a Google service
account. Um and so we really got to keep
our eyes open for these. And then the
other sha shout out was uh that he said
a lot of times what happened was uh pe
people would just commit binary files
such as pyc files right and not
realizing because that's a binary file
you know they're looking at it and
they're like okay that doesn't have
anything insensitive in it that
definitely does have something it's like
a code review uh bypass kind of path.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean you can you can
decompile those things a lot of times
and the strings are just going to be in
there. And I remember at a live hacking
event back in the day, I saw a finding
that was just like super super good. And
one best bug of the event where uh the
the guy found it exactly in the same way
that where somebody had committed a
certificate to log into a GitHub um you
know organization uh inside of a like
binary SQL file. Wow. Uh and no one had
found it. But then as he was grepping
through it, he he stumbled upon it, was
able to extract theert and off into the
uh the the hosted GitHub and it was like
it was really bad. So this is definitely
a big thing paying extra attention to
binary files is important. Make sure you
add that dash a on uh on your rip gp or
your gp if you're grapping across stuff.
Mhm. Yeah. I still uh like you said
because of Tom Nom Nom do like GP dash
HR NIA or whatever like uh anytime I'm
ging uh just because of those initial
videos from him and Stoke and stuff like
that. So very cool. Yeah. So I yeah I
wanted to roll that into the tool that I
released. Um
I don't Yeah, it doesn't make it doesn't
make sense for a good share. Um do you
want to talk about pop up a bunch of t
Yeah, I mean I just and it's funny
because it was on my list, not your
list. Um, but it it's essentially, you
know, you you release this tool where um
it's just a really simple website tool
where you just go in there, you put in a
domain, and it pops up like 15 pop-ups
in your browser uh that that are like,
"Hey, uh here's Google, GitHub, Wayback
Machine, Showdown, uh Security Trails,
SH, Chacht, Census, all of these, you
know, places where you would normally
scrape data." Um uh and and oftentimes
people have like scripts for all that,
but you just kind of did it right in the
browser, which I I I think has a sort of
attractive quick and dirty nature to it,
right? Where it's like, okay, you know,
I don't not necessarily at my setup
right now, but I kind of want to do some
preliminary recon on this thing. Let me
just drop this uh domain in here and,
you know, make sure I'm not missing any
of these places where I could find
additional assets. Yeah, for me
personally, it's like when I'm hacking
and I'm like in a JavaScript file and I
find a random dev subdomain, that's when
I would use something like this. It's
like I'll just throw this in here
because it's so useful for it to pop up
like in a GitHub search because then
it's like usually in one of their repos
or one of their employees, right? So, it
comes up in that GitHub search and then
just kind of having all of the rest of
that pop up at the same time is really
useful. I did notice a lot of people
were like, "All this does is open
Google." It's like, yeah, it is actually
confusing. So, when I ran this tool the
first time on my computer, I got a popup
that was like, "Do you want to open more
pop-ups and I was able to just approve
it, but then hackluke was me and him
were hanging out and talking and stuff
and he cloned it onto his website and so
I went and used it on his website. It
didn't give me that pop-up." I had to
manually go into
Chrome: settings and like browse for his
website and then go enable it. So, if
you try to use this tool, like make sure
you enable pop-ups so that they all
appear. And, you know, you can just look
at the source of this page and make your
own copy. You don't have to use mine,
but I think it's just a really nice way
to pull up all of the different like
kind of Google dorks. And someone could
also clone this tool and make it do a
bunch of Google dorks. The issue is
because it's coming from one IP and one
user agent, you will get um you will get
those really annoying uh captures at
some point. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Well, it
worked for me too. You know, the first
time I I just, you know, put in a domain
and I pressed launch and it popped up
one. But then if you go back to the
actual, you know, your website, it'll
say allow this website to pop up
multiple pop-ups. And I pressed allow
and ran it again and it went and it like
popped all of them out. Um, so I think I
think it's most people that have an
interest in using this tool can figure
out how to actually use it. Um, so
helpful, I think. So good job there,
man. Cool. Yeah, no problem. I love
those little like tiny tools. Um, all
right. Uh, let's see. I have a really
small one since that one was technically
on your list. Um, I just there's a very
small group of listeners that like care
a lot about local models. Um, they're
probably, you know, some of the most
privacy and security conscious and I
just I love um, you know, following the
AI space. Simon Wilson mentioned that
the new Quinn 3 um, especially the 8bit
model even at 4-bit quantized, but even
at full size, it still can run on most
MacBook Pros or on like most um, GPUs,
like if you have a gaming computer,
right, that you hack from or whatever,
you can run it, too. And so, anyways, I
was going to recommend that. It seems
like it's the best at that model size
and 8 billion parameters is small enough
where uh especially at 4-bit quantize
you can run it with 16 gig gigabytes of
RAM. So if you have like an old M1 or M2
and it's only got 16 gig of RAM, you can
run this pretty efficiently on like your
little computer laptop. And I think um
you know a lot of people are like well
what would you do with it? I think there
are a lot of like kind of interesting um
you know write for me or summarize this
tasks that like let's say you have a
thousand URLs that you want it to like
um that you know you can like curl the
the the um request or you can curl the
JavaScript or whatever and then just
return that to the local model and just
say describe this and you go to sleep
and you have it do that across all of
them like a lot of like overnight
running tasks where you don't want to
buy the token cost um you can use these
kind of local models for well and and I
think there's a privacy piece of that
too that right where um one of the
things that Jason said when he came on
the podcast last time uh was that you
can use these local models for simply
for redaction so so you know you say
okay hey here's an HTTP request redact
any identifying factors on this right
and then and then you send the redacted
API you know uh request to you know a
state-of-the-art uh model and then it
can do its thing right without knowing
what target you're on and that sort of
thing so I think that's valid and then I
think also you like we have for Shift,
dude. Um, for for Shift, it's not
sending your data to the AI unless you
specifically ask it to, right? The only
exception to that is when you turn on AI
rename uh for your for your tabs, for
your replay tabs within within um Kaido.
Uh, and then it sends every, you know,
replay request that you have out to to
the uh to the AI. And I was thinking,
ah, it'd be really nice if we had
something like a very small local model
that could just look at our HTTP
requests and do the thing that we tell
it to do. Like, hey, rename this. It's
so low stakes. It's like, who cares if
it's wrong? Who cares if whatever. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. And if it makes small
mistakes, it's not the end of the world.
It's just better, you know, to have the
things renamed the way we want them
renamed, right? Um, so I think this
could be a really good use case for
this, too. Yeah. If people have like
little tiny tools they want to run
locally that do small tasks like that,
it's a great idea. Actually, in the
tweet, um, Simon said that it only uses
four to five gigabytes of RAM while it's
running. Well, that's Yeah, that's
because he's using the full bit four-bit
quantise. And then also, you never want
it to use all of your RAM. So, that's
why I said it's perfect if you have like
16 gig of RAM because Chrome's going to
take up eight, you know, and then most
people don't want to close everything
down to run their AI model. So, yeah,
that's what's great about it is that it
only uses that much. Yep. I have 16
gigabytes of RAM. Open Chrome, you have
4 GB of RAM. Exactly. Matt, you can use
the AI. Yeah. Um, all right, man. Uh,
yeah. So, next up, uh, I guess I'll I'll
I'll take this next one. Yeah. Um, there
was an article released, uh, entitled
May Cause Pwnage. Um, this is on, uh, I
I I'm going to butcher this guy's name,
but Jisol. Jaisol. Yeah, sounds right.
Jaisol. Yeah, sounds about right. Um, on
his blog, and it was in collaboration
with Jorian, um, who's very active in
the, uh, CTB community. And essentially
this is an audit of um MCP protocols and
uh some kind of vulnerabilities that
have been happening in them. And it's
definitely a good read for any of you
guys that are interested in sort of
getting ahead of this curve on AI
adoption. So as these companies start
implementing, excuse me, start
implementing um MCP uh uh protocol for
their various utilities, then uh this is
something we're going to have to be on
the lookout for. Um and it's often
running on non-standard ports. And it
you can see right here, man,
Like one of the first things that on the
list is getbased curve to command
injection and I'm like oh no and it's
crazy how simple this exploit is. It
it's like literally SSE transport
transport type is uh stdio and then
command equals calc.exe and it just pops
calc I'm like no. Um so very impactful
stuff here. uh they cover how to do DNS
rebinding to attack this uh environment
and extract data um and a bunch of other
vulnerabilities where they sort of uh
spread scanned across the internet to
try to identify these these MCP servers
and and got a lot of I think it was like
104 um command and control servers uh
that could have been stood up uh across
the whole internet. So definitely some
good research here. Yeah. Yeah. And
what's insane is like, you know, when we
when we had mentioned MCP security being
an issue, you know, because if you have
multiple tools and there's like some
sort of prompt injection in one, then it
can like execute in the other like for
that COG.exe for example, right? If that
was chained with something else that was
browsing the web and you have prompt
injection on your site that says, "Hey,
pop this command." Then the the one that
does the command exec can actually pop
it, right? But these bugs are just in
the protocol like and in the
implementation like these aren't even
using prompt injection in any way, shape
or form, right? So, I think MCP is like
a really really great spot for people to
dig in and research like you said
because companies are going to be
releasing them. I've met with a few
startups that are already implementing
them. Um, and some of them have already
released them. These are not companies
that I know of that have bug bounty
programs yet, but like it's coming. So,
especially if people didn't know this,
OpenAI and Google have both agreed to
use MCP. It's obviously it was like um
released and invented by Anthropic, but
like the other providers are have
accepted it. So, um, by by leaning into
it, you're not, you know, only doing
research on a thin slice or something.
You're doing research on something on a
protocol that's going to be used by
everyone. So, help me understand the use
case of this a little bit because I'm
I'm still a little bit of fuzzy. The
this is enabling the AI to execute tools
on a specific service provider. Is that
right? Now, is that typically like an an
API? So, like, you know, whatever seats.
you know, exposes a a uh you know, MCP
server and now the AI can interact
directly with seats. Or yes, is it
something? That's exactly right. Yeah.
So many people are like MCP is just an
API. It's like yeah, you're not wrong,
but at the same time, it's really
important because like let's say that
you're seeds. And you want to expose
your API? Do you want every developer
and every um AI client to have to
reimplement your tool call, right? or
even if even if you have like a GitHub
repo they can go clone from and add or
like something they can go copy and
paste into their code they support it.
It just is still too abstract, right? So
MCP streamlines that where basically you
stand up the MCP server now any MCP
client of which there are not a lot yet
but of which there are becoming more and
more. So like wind surf cursor and like
the claw desktop app are like the most
used by far in those MCP clients you can
just put in your MCP config the uh the
tools you want it to have exposed and
that there there's still a lot of
ambiguity there and implementation
details that are not ironed out fully
like some people are doing it different
ways but basically you just add the tool
to your MCP client's config and now you
don't have to worry about implementing
the documentation or explaining to your
AI how to write the query. or naming the
tool and all those things. It was done
by the MCP server and u author basically
and so then now any client can connect
to that server. Nice. Nice. Yeah. So, I
imagine this is one of the things that
we'll also see, you know, for the recon
boys out there, you might want to put
some stuff in there where you start
fingerprinting these things as they spin
up because I imagine what'll happen is
like there'll be some uh, you know,
server that is exposed uh, some internal
server, right, that was supposed to be
internal, but it's external and it's
exposing MCP so that uh, other, you
know, pieces of AI in the organization,
right, can reach out to this thing and
interact with it. Um, and then but if
that's actually exposed to the internet,
then boom, you know, you're in big
trouble sort of. Yeah. And honestly, you
won't know when those are changed under
the hood because you're not going to
want to push uh updates to the clients
or anything. So, you may even want to
like when you said fingerprint, I
thought you were going to say like
fingerprint how they're responding like
if they have like version numbers like
you know maybe the MCP server has a
version call or if not um basically
retesting is going to be really valuable
here because if they if they mess up O
where let's say they have they
implemented OOTH or something where
you're only supposed to have access to
your data if you like ask the MP server
to give you someone else's data it's not
going to work at first but if they have
a regression or they implement a bug
down the road or something then you
would you would catch that if you're
retesting. Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely. And I
imagine the MCP server has to have some
sort of introspection, right, to to be
able to tell the the AI, you know, hey,
these are the tools that it has to have
like notes like, hey, here's how you
format your request. And then that gets
used in the context. Yeah. So, it should
be super easy to sort of monitor change
logs, so to speak, on what functions are
being exposed by the MCP servers. Well,
whatever ones they disclose to you.
What's interesting is that a lot of
these on the back end will probably have
other API routes created, but then not
in the notes, like not in the not in the
tool notes that get past the AI. So, if
you can actually just like there's
probably some fun exploration and deep
research, which isn't as scannable, but
where you can go in and be like, "Hey,
let's just see if there's any other
routes. Just try this route or try this
route or try this patch reversal or
whatever." Yeah. I mean, and and if
you're looking at the rest of the
vulnerabilities in this write up,
there's like, you know, uh SSRF, local
file disclosure, more rce, you know, git
command injection. Yeah, it's like
there's a ton of stuff in here. Yeah.
So, um definitely a ripe environment
both for recon boys and for uh the rest
of us. Y um all right, so that that's
that. Um let's go ahead and and bump
down uh to your next one. Okay. So, by
the way, you you had this on here, the
the no XSS um uh you know, WFT bypass or
whatever. Yeah, dude. Like this. Okay,
sure. Maybe this is a W bypass. Like,
this got like a thousand uh likes on it,
but import is like the most standard way
to to like load an external resource. I
just thought it was I just thought it
was hilarious and I was like, you know,
people people want things to try and so
it's awesome to have something to try,
right?
Yeah. Yeah. I mean it is it is um for
me, you know, this this is uh like the
go-to way to import a script. Yeah. Like
like this is like try a script tag when
you're doing XSS sort of situation. Um
but it but it is uh it is definitely
good to be aware of and and some hackers
that I've seen recently didn't know that
you could dynamically import JavaScript
um you know without having to create you
know a script tag or like fetch the data
and uh and then you know evalid or
something like that via the import
function call. So it's a good it's a
good call. Yeah. I mean I've never used
the import um function call so maybe
that's why it was like super interesting
I threw it in there. Yeah. Yeah. Well
there's lots of data to there's lots of
you know ways to smuggle data through.
So, um, that's a good one. All right,
dude. Let me, um, let me let me show you
this. Uh, now I'm going to flex a little
bit. Uh, so, okay. So, dude, we we're
we're recording this on, uh, May 7th,
right? This is going to be released May
8th. Thank you, production team. Um, and
I have not pushed this plugin to the
Kaido store yet, and I'm going to do
that tonight. I'm sure you will. So
hopefully it'll be hopefully it'll be um
released uh by the time that this
podcast airs. But uh I'm creating a new
a new plugin called drop okay for Kaido
and it is super helpful for sharing
various uh objects from uh person to
person. So let's say you know so I'm
going to show you how it works right
here. Uh you open up drop and it gives
you a share code right here right and
then you pass that share code to your
friend and this is your PGP public key
right here. Everything is end to end
encrypted for this. And um once you give
your friend you know your public key
then your friend can encrypt data with
your public key chuck it up to the
server and then you sign something you
know saying hey I'm I have the private
key for this public key give me all the
messages for this public key. You
download that message decrypt it with
the private key and then you um you know
ingest these specific objects into your
Kaido instance after you have a chance
to assess them. Um, and so, uh, you can
get messages. Hopefully, I'm gonna try
to do a live demo right now. We'll see
if it works. So, scope dropped to Justin
Gardner, right? And then you get a
notification saying, "Hey, you got a
drop from Justin Gardner. Here's the
scope. Would you like to claim it?" You
press claim. And now, you know, you've
got another scope right here in your in
your um, Kaido environment. So, you can
we can right now we can share filters,
scopes, match and replace, and replay
tabs. Match and replace is going to be a
really clutch one. A lot of times when
I'm collaborating with other people,
they'll be like, "Oh, I figured it out.
I got the matcher place work on the
client side so that I can like see all
the routes, you know, or whatever." And
being able to like immediately share
that's cool. Yeah. Yeah. So, it should
be super great for collaboration. I feel
like this is we talked about this,
right? This is like called like the
Kieran callbacks. We'll call that that
section. Didn't Kieran make a Justin
Nerd Sniper plugin like a year ago or
something for Kaido that was like
nerdype Justin, but I think it used
Discord web hooks. This is much more
This is much more collaborative send
back and forth, but this reminds me very
strongly of that. Yeah. You know, and
you can hook into a like a specific web
hook to like dump dump it in a channel
or something, but I wanted something
that just allows me to send it to your
Kaido instance directly, you know? So,
if we're collaborating, you literally
just have a message pop up that says
claim, you know, or like new drop from
Justin. Here's this request. And you
have claim or delete, right? You press
claim and boom, it's in your it's in
your replay, you know, and you can just,
you know, tweak it. And I don't I don't
want to do bugs or anything like if I if
my Kaido's closed and you've sent like
12 and I open it up, will they be
sitting there waiting? They will. Yeah.
Yeah. They they sit on the server for 7
days. Y um unless they're claimed,
right? And if they're claimed, they're
stored locally in your Kaido. Um but
after seven days, they're gone. So if
your homie is just not collabing with
you at all and you're spamming your
homie, uh then it's you it's not going
to fly.
Is there is there is there anything
besides the popup? Like does it also
show up in the drop tab or something?
Yeah. Yeah. Hold on. Let me show you let
me show you one more time as well cuz
you know there there's a little popup
that will pop up on the um on the
screen, right? So if we go right here
and I drop to myself, right? There's
this little popup that pops up at the
right hand corner. Let's see. There it
is right here. Right. Cool. But I can
close this, right? Say I don't want to
address that right now. And I can go to
drop and go to received messages. And
here's the message right here. And then
you can claim or delete. Dude, such a
cool plugin idea. Yeah, I think this I
think this will be great. I also want to
develop something where um even without
knowing your public key, I can uh create
like a link that says, "Hey, uh here's
here's like this request, right?" And it
just encrypts it uh and then maybe
passes you the the uh shared secret or
whatever via a hash in a URL or
something. And then um and then you know
once you put that link into Kaido it
will uh download the specific request
decrypt the um you know encrypted data
and then give you an opportunity to
claim that object whatever. That's
really cool. Yeah. I I I really want the
the Kaido you know I I want this to be a
really collaboration rich environment.
Yeah. Um and I think that will help with
it a lot. Yeah. This is going to be
awesome. I can't wait to use it. Yeah.
So hopefully this will be on the HKO
tour by tonight. Uh, I am still running
it on my local dev server, but I have
some time allocated later today to get
everything pushed to prod. Um, and it'll
be out there. Cool. I'm going to jump to
Andre's. Um, sure. Just in general, I
think Andre's been uh killing it lately
on he's been pushing out good content.
He has been.
Um the question is uh whether it's him
or Hackluke, but uh we uh uh one thing
that's really great about this is uh
like the little things that uh he's been
posting is that I feel like it's a bunch
of stuff to be honest that feels like
it's in this vein of like really cool
research or really cool um uh techniques
that people haven't really or at least
that I personally haven't incorporated
into my testing flow like strongly. And
like you know a good example um is like
the smuggled uh like what are these
called again? Encoded word. And yeah
basically encoded words. I never check
for this which in general I think it's
kind of hard to test for things that you
have to like redo the full signup flow
for each time which you know may maybe
this one you don't. you know, you can go
in and like change your email in a lot
of apps, but anytime there is a um you
know, like kind of a bug or like a a
testing thing that happens as a result
of like uh what you do during sign up
and you have to like go confirm your
account and all that, I'm like kind of
lazy with that in the past and I think
that I'm going to change that now and
like kind of lean into testing more
stuff like this. Um yeah, I don't know.
Do you have any thoughts? It it it's
it's pivotal to do that. I mean, it
really is like uh the amount of times
that I've gone to a live hacking event
and I've been busting my ass like to
configure all these things and find
these really obscure crits and then
Andre just walks in and he's like,
"Yeah, I threw this like weird unicode
character in there and now I've got
arbitrary ATO." And I'm like, "Screw
you, dude." Seriously though, it's it's
it's too real. Um and somehow Andre
always finds arbitrary ATO via like this
email related garbage. And I'm like, how
do you do this? Well, I wonder if he
does basically like objective based
hacking. I don't know. I'm sure you've
discussed that on the podcast. We've
discussed that on the pod before, but I
talk a lot about that with um with
Douglas and Kieran is like sometimes
when you're constrained, especially a
life hacking like a hardened target. If
you just set like a really hardcore goal
and then just aggressively pursue that,
the constraint like um breeds creativity
in like your things that you're
attempting. Yeah, 100%. And man, I've
done this a couple times in live hacking
events and I've gotten them every time
and I'm like, "Wow, this is nuts." Like,
like if I really just lock in on like,
you know, one thing, I'm thinking of a
specific uh live hacking event in
particular where I was surprised where I
was like, "Okay, my goal is to do creepy
[__] with this app, you know, and
yeah, it was there's one there's one in
London and then there was also one in in
Vegas as well." I was like, like this is
what I want to accomplish, you know, and
then somehow it happened and I'm like,
okay. Like maybe everything is possible.
You just got to keep poking at it.
Exactly. Yeah. Yeah. So anyway, yeah,
Andre Andre is nuts, man, because I do
remember one time where we were at a
life hacking event and the team set out
a challenge and we were all like, "Haha,
that's cute." Like they're they're
putting 100k bounty on this thing or
like 70k bounty. It's impossible. Yeah.
And it's impossible. And then Andre's
like found it like 20 less than 24 hours
after the challenge was released. And
I'm like, "Oh my gosh." And it was like
a 15year-old bug, too. It was crazy.
It's crazy. That's awesome. Um, all
right. Um, okay. Last thing on the list
for me was uh, dude, Nah is just around
the corner, man. And we haven't shouted
it out on the pod yet. So, um, if any of
you guys are not aware, our boy Nah,
Ben, uh, like does this conference every
year that is just very much bug bounty
relevant. Um, and this year they've got
AI related stuff and you've got bug
bounty related stuff. Um, you know, you
might you might see your boy hosting,
who knows? Uh, you might see your boy
Reszo giving a presentation. Um, so
definitely want to check that out. Uh
you can find at
nahcon.com. I I'm just gonna read some
of the titles out here. Yeah. Like uh
yeah, you grab the dates. I'll uh I
believe it's the 22nd and the 23rd. May
22nd. 23rd. Yep. And uh and so here's
the the first day schedule. Okay. You
got the keynote by um Jay Hadex Reszo
Namese. You got uh XSS doctor uh doing a
talk on AI assisted hacking. You got
Wonder Wuzzy, another uh person that
came on the pod talking about advanced
prompt injection exploits in LLM apps.
Uh you've got your boy Reszo again, a AI
findings in Bug Bounty. You got Mon,
another uh pod veteran uh talking about
uh how hacking how we learn speedr
runninging bug bounty proficiency with
AI. You got Jay Hatex on modern AI
assessment. And you got Daniel Measler
with AI capabilities for attackers and
defenders. What a stacked lineup, dude.
Like that is crazy. So definitely going
to be tuning into that. That would
that's just AI day. Day two is Tom Nom
Nom JRock Insider PhD. Oh my gosh. Renee
Pac, Arman Samir. Yeah. Yeah, dude. So
many of these people are are have come
on the pod, too. It's great. I mean, the
community the community is tight, right?
So, yeah, it is. It is. So, definitely
check it out. Um, Day 2 also looks
awesome. You've got GraphQL stuff.
You've got cookie uh counterfeiting.
You've got Tom Nom Nom. Whenever Tom Nom
Nom puts anything out, you should
definitely check that out%. Yeah. And
then I I think one of the most
underestimated hackers out there is
Broomman's dude. Like this guy puts out
some really really good vans and uh and
all of his stuff that he does for Yes,
we hack as well. Yeah. Is like super
high top. Yeah. Yeah. Definitely
something to check out. Uh the last
thing I wanted to cover uh was this Ply
thing that's obviously AI related.
basically um Ply who we've talked about
a lot does a lot of jailbreaking and AI
hacking and stuff. He um he shared the
like system prompt league for Gemini 2
Pro with Canvas and it one it's just
interesting and good to read but two uh
somebody maybe the other person on this
uh recording right now has found some
good bugs in Gemini Pro canvas. So um
the canvas is like a really interesting
thing to hack, right? because it's like
basically like a little mini compiler or
or like not really compiler but it
basically can like execute the code that
that um Gemini Yeah. It's a code
execution environment built into the
LLM. Yeah. Right. And it has so many
little weird nuances and quirks and and
even in AI Studio there's also now like
these like starter apps that are kind of
in there. And so I think that um uh
where was I going with that? Um the the
like I mean this and did you see the the
tweet by Logan as well that was uh close
to this where they just listed out like
all of the freaking Google employees
that were building really cool [__] in
Canvas on like oneshot prompts like this
thing is pretty is pretty powerful.
Yeah, it's really powerful. I mean one
people should use it I think in general.
Uh and I actually gave you this tip
Justin so I'll go ahead and give it to
listeners and it worked really well for
you. Yeah. uh if you're building things
with AI and it feels like such a like a
silly or trivial tip, but it works
extremely well. Basically, if you're
using AI to like write some code for
you, instead of giving it, you know, a a
vague description of what you want or
even a 70% description of what you want,
that 30% when the AI's in there
modifying like multiple files and stuff
will basically mean you loop a lot and
you end up with a lot of little bugs
that you then have to work through over
time. If you can get your spec, like
your description of what you want to
more like requirement document, PRD.
Yeah, PRD. Like if you can get a perfect
or like a sorry, a verbose product
requirement document that's like 90 to
100% of what you want. The new AI models
and I haven't even used the new Gemini
Pro model that came out yesterday that's
even better at coding will basically
oneshot your idea even if it's across
multiple files or whatever. So the tip
here and like anytime you hear a leading
a person who's at the bleeding edge of
tech say something which uh in this case
was Andre Kaparthy that I saw and then
another guy that I love it's probably
the best AI engineer I know his name is
Harishi like Karishi was DMing me the
same thing that Kaparthy had said and he
hadn't read what Kaparthi said. So
basically these two guys converge on the
same insight and wisdom which is
basically spend more time than you think
you need to coming up with that product
requirement document and you can do it
in Gemini 2 canvas which we just
mentioned right. So if you open Gemini
and then you like enable the canvas tab
just just say like hey I want to build
this app give me a PRD you know it'll
know what it is for that thing so that I
can read it and refine it and then as
you're reading it you'll say you'll see
things where it's ambiguous like it'll
be like it'll just say like backend text
stack and you'll say no I want the
backend to use specifically this text
stack you know and I want it to work in
this specific way anyways just iterate
on that a few times and then give that
PRD to an AI model to build it and
you're going to get a much higher
quality thing but anyways I
Let me just say on that as well, dude.
Two things. One, one of the biggest
takeaways from the Google live hacking
event that we did was Gemini is freaking
awesome. Like it it is an amazing
amazing amazing uh AI tool. So don't
don't sleep on Gemini just in, you know,
efficiency of life sort of things. Um
and two, just to support what you said,
drop the the um the credit plugin that I
was just telling you about for
collaboration. It's got a bunch of, you
know, it's got endto-end encryption.
It's got, uh, you know, some custom UI
components that interact with Kaido. Um,
I spent a long time doing what you said.
I went to Gemini. I said, "Hey, let's
build a PRD for this. Here are the
specs. Here's what I want to do. Here's
the backend component. Here's the
front-end component." Um, and it
completely oneshotted the backend
component. Like I probably if you have
an idea for Kaido plugin, do what Justin
just did. Do what we just said. Do a
PRD. Give it the context of how Kaido
plugins work. like the you know the repo
or whatever the read me and then it will
potentially oneshot the entire solution.
Yeah. And the UI it generated was
amazing and like I mean and the front
end I had to tweak a bunch because I was
like uh hooking into Kaido UI and like
all sorts of stuff like that but but um
the back end it completely one-shot it
and like this is crazy. Yeah, it's
really cool. It's super cool. Um, so
anyways, where I was going with the
mentioning the canvas is not just the
fact that the canvas is there and that
you can get the system prompt from that
link that we'll put in the show notes,
but there are just like so many other
little AI features that Google's adding
across the board. You know, we're
passionate about like hacking on them
and stuff. They just added gems in
Workspace. Um, and so anyways, lots of
cool stuff to hack on. I just want to
give that to listeners so they had
something to, you know, go hack on this
week if they didn't have anything to
look at. Yeah, 100%. Very cool stuff. Um
uh we've got like two minutes, so I'm
gonna cover this last thing really
quickly from um Gareth Hayes uh that was
actually in your in your uh docket here,
but Gareth tweeted something out. And
this is like I think just a perfect
example of what we talk about when we're
saying, "Hey, just like tell the
community about cool [__] right? So
that so that we can all understand
better how this cluster of JavaScript
works, man. It's like it's amazing." Um,
and so, uh, Gareth tweeted out, I think
it was around April 25th, uh, uh,
earlier and said, "Hey, there's
something really weird with SVG related
onload, uh, handlers." And there's this,
uh, when you console.log the actual
onload handler from an SVG onload um,
uh, onclick event, you know, or or what
is that event handler uh, attribute in
HTML? That's what I'm trying to say. um
then it it looks very different or or
very slightly different from what you
would see when you look at an image tag
on on loader on error handler. Um the
difference is that there is a different
event parameter that is is being passed.
one is um event and the other one is
EVT. And he was speculating on why
that's the case, but um the the TLDDR of
the situation is that uh it actually
provides a way for you to get a DOM
reference inside of that onload handler.
Um so you can do
evt.composed
path.pop.default view. One, right? So
that default view gives you the document
reference and then alert one uh you know
or default view gives you the window and
then you can run alert one on that. And
um he he shouted this out and I think
it's relevant for anybody who uh that
likes JavaScript based sandboxes. If you
have a sandbox, you've got to look out
for this because this can result in a
DOM object leak which can be really
impactful in those sandbox scenarios.
Um, so if you're find yourself stuck in
a in a sandbox and you can't um get a
reference to the document, then you
might be able to use an SVG onload uh
event to, you know, go down that path
that Gareth described here and get a
reference to the document object. Yeah,
I'm, you know, not a very strong
JavaScript person, but like when I
whenever he when I was reading this and
I saw that EBT pop up with like that
conversion, I'm just like, what what are
they doing? Whatird? It's so weird.
Yeah. And and he says, I suspect that
this is a workound to accommodate IE
quirks because there's a a global
window.event. So there could there's
like some namespace conflicts, you know,
that sort of thing. So, um, definitely
definitely a cool thing to note by
Gareth here. And he says, and I'll just
read this line at the end. Uh, it says,
"There isn't really a conclusion to
this, and I'm just happy to blog things
about things that I find interesting in
any way. I hope you enjoyed it." Which
is just, yes, do that for everything.
Everyone, everyone, please do that. But
yes, thank you. Give him a round of
applause. Yes. Teach us more about this
crazy land of JavaScript. We want to
know everything so that we can
understand how to break it, right? Um,
and I think that's the pod. Am I right?
Yeah, dude. Yeah. Thank you all for
listening. Good work. Sorry the Google
episode's not out. And uh I've also
recorded the second part of the AI
series. So that'll either if Google's
not ready next week, that can come out
next week. If not, it'll be the week
after. So yeah. All right. GG, guys.
Peace.
And that's a wrap on this episode of
Critical Thinking. Thanks so much for
watching to the end, y'all. If you want
more critical thinking content, uh or if
you want to support the show, head over
to
ctb.show/isord. You can hop in the
community. There's lots of great
highlevel hacking discussion happening
there on top of master classes,
hackalongs, exclusive content, and a
full-time hunter guild. If you're a
full-time hunter, it's a great time.
Trust me. All right, I'll see you there.